WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
(GRUNTING)
I lost this dagger.
To whom?
Tyrion Lannister.
Take a step toward a more
productive relationship
with a possible ally.
I will allow you to mine
the dragonglass
and forge weapons from it.
Thank you.
RANDYLL TARLY: She has three
full-grown dragons, Your Grace.
How do you propose to stop them?
We are currently at work
on a solution.
(THUDDING)
(HORSE BRAYING)
HOT PIE: I thought
you'd be heading for Winterfell.
Jon Snow came down
from Castle Black
with a wildling army and won
the Battle of the Bastards.
He's King in the North now.
(GRUNTING)
COMMANDER: Your sister's dead.
THEON: Euron has her.
I couldn't save her.
I tried.
You wouldn't be here
if you'd tried.
What about Casterly Rock?
(ROARING)
(GRUNTING)
TYCHO NESTORIS: We both know
how expensive war can be.
Your vaults are empty.
My debt will be paid in full.
How will it happen?
Will there be pain?
JAIME: No. I made sure of that.
I'd hate to die like your son.
Not at all what I intended.
Tell Cersei.
I want her to know it was me.
( theme music playing )
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com
( horse neighs )
MAN: Hold that wagon!
( horses neighing )
You've just won the biggest
prize in the world.
What could you possibly
have to be upset about?
Come on, you can tell me.
Queen of Thorns give you one
last prick in the balls
before saying goodbye?
I'll save my confessions
for the High Septon.
There is no more High Septon.
No, there isn't, is there?
There is still
the question of my prize.
That's a lot of money
I just gave you.
It's not a castle.
How about that one?
It's available.
You don't want Highgarden.
- I beg to differ.
- We're at war.
Daenerys Targaryen could come and take
it back the day after you move in.
Besides, think of the upkeep.
The more you owe,
the more it weighs you down.
Oh, is that why
you're so fucking glum, eh?
All your new riches
weighing you down?
- MAN: Move out!
- JAIME: They're not mine.
This all belongs
to the Iron Bank.
See?
We pay our debts.
Right, just not to me.
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater,
formerly of...
whatever nameless
shit heap you're from
with a saddlebag full of gold,
complaining about
not getting paid.
When we win this war,
all the castles
in the Seven Kingdoms
will be yours to choose from,
with no one left
to take them away from you.
Yes, I'm sure
Queen Cersei's reign
will be quiet and peaceable.
Ah, stranger things
have happened.
Like what?
The granaries are being emptied
and loaded into wagons, my lord.
- The current harvest?
- We have teams of men collecting it
from all the farms in the Reach.
Ser Bronn, will you
accompany the Tarlys
and help them
accelerate this process?
I'm not much
for shoveling wheat.
No, but motivating reluctant farmers
to hand over their harvest--
I bet you're going to have
a real talent for that.
My lord.
TYCHO: I must say, I don't
think the Iron Bank
has ever had a debt of this magnitude
repaid in a single installment.
I always considered your father a
very effective and efficient man,
but you appear to be redefining
those terms entirely.
You're too kind, my lord.
I am neither kind
nor a lord, Your Grace.
I am merely an instrument of
the institution I represent.
Its well-being is a matter
of arithmetic, not sentiment.
And the current arithmetic
is outstanding.
- Uh, the gold...
- Is on its way.
My brother is supervising
its transportation himself.
Some at the Iron Bank
will be disappointed.
They've grown rather fond
of your interest payments.
We must devise a way
to raise their spirits.
Yes, perhaps we could
be of assistance
in some current venture.
My only venture at this moment
is reestablishing control
over this continent
and every person on it.
I see a great deal
of potential in that venture.
I imagine it would require
outside investment.
It will, indeed.
I need to expand
my armies, my navies.
My Hand, Qyburn, has made overtures
to the Golden Company in Essos.
I know them well.
They have helped us
recover significant sums
from parties who had
fallen into deep arrears.
That's good to hear.
I, too, would like them to recover
some things that belong to me.
Rest assured, Your Grace,
you can count on
the Iron Bank's support.
- Hmm.
- As soon as the gold arrives.
( fire crackling )
LITTLEFINGER: This is for you.
The last man who wielded it
meant to cut your throat,
but your mother fought him off.
The other dagger,
the one that took her life,
I would have stopped that
dagger with my own heart
if I could have.
I wasn't there for her
when she needed me most.
But I am here for her now
to do what she would have done,
to protect her children.
Anything I can do
for you, Brandon,
you need only ask.
Do you know
who this belonged to?
No.
That very question was what started
the War of the Five Kings.
In a way, that dagger made
you what you are today.
Forced from your home,
driven out to the wilds
beyond the Wall.
I imagine you've seen things
most men wouldn't believe.
To go through all of that
and make your way home again
only to find such chaos
in the world,
I can only imagine--
Chaos is a ladder.
( door opens )
( exhales )
I'm sorry to have
disturbed you, Lord Stark.
I'm not Lord Stark.
What's that?
Maester Wolkan built it for me
so I can move around
more easily.
It's a very good idea.
You're leaving.
I don't want to leave you,
but when--
when they come,
I need to be with my family.
And you're safe.
Well, as safe
as anyone can be now.
You don't need me anymore.
No, I don't.
That's all you've got to say?
Thank you.
Thank you?
For helping me.
My brother died for you.
Hodor and Summer died for you.
I almost died for you.
- Bran...
- I'm not, really.
Not anymore.
( crying )
I remember what it felt
like to be Brandon Stark,
but I remember so much else now.
You died in that cave.
I did.
The kitchen girl,
the redhead with the behind.
The only thing in the kitchen that
you've put your cock in is the liver.
'Ey up.
Where you going?
In there.
I live here.
( snickers )
Fuck off.
I'm Arya Stark.
This is my home.
( Henk snorts )
Arya Stark's dead.
Send for Maester Luwin
or Ser Rodrick.
- They'll tell you who I am.
- There's no Rodrick here.
Maester's named Wolkan.
Go ask Jon Snow, then,
the King in the North.
- He's my brother.
- He's a thousand miles away.
Look, it's cold and we're busy,
- so, you know, best fuck off.
- Mm.
If Jon's gone, who's in
charge of Winterfell?
The Lady of Winterfell.
Lady Stark.
- Which Lady Stark?
- HENK: You tell us.
You're the one
impersonating her sister.
Tell Sansa her sister's home.
Lady Sansa is too busy to waste
her breath on you, just like us.
So, for the last time, fuck off.
( grunts )
I'm getting into this castle
one way or another.
If I'm not who I say I am,
I won't last long.
But if I am and Sansa finds
out you turned me away...
Right, you sit there.
Right there.
Don't move.
Right, go tell Lady Stark.
I'll watch her.
HENK: I ain't telling Lady Stark.
You can tell her.
KONER: Why me?
- HENK: You're gonna tell her.
- I'm not.
'Cause if you don't, I'm gonna hit
you right in the fucking face
as hard as I can.
KONER: We told her to wait.
( sighs ) We were standing
right next to her, and...
And-- and when we turned
around, she'd gone, my lady.
She-- she was nothing.
Some winter town girl.
She comes in asking
for, uh, Ser Rodrick...
- Rodrick, yeah. Luwin, yeah.
- ...and Maester Luwin.
( Henk stammering ) And don't
trouble yourself over it, my lady.
- We'll-- we'll find her.
- You don't have to.
I know where she is.
( fire crackling )
( chain rattling )
Do I have to call you
Lady Stark now?
Yes.
You shouldn't have run
from the guards.
I didn't run.
You need better guards.
( chuckles )
It suits you...
Lady Stark.
Jon left you in charge?
He did.
I hope he comes back soon.
I remember how happy
he was to see me.
When he sees you, his
heart will probably stop.
( chuckles )
It doesn't look like him.
Should've been carved
by someone who knew his face.
Everyone who knew
his face is dead.
We're not.
They say you killed Joffrey.
Did you?
I wish I had.
Hmm.
Me, too.
I was angry when I heard
someone else had done it.
However long my list got,
he was always first.
Your list?
Of people I'm going to kill.
How did you get back
to Winterfell?
It's a long story.
I imagine yours is, too.
Yes.
Not a very pleasant one.
Mine neither.
But our stories aren't over yet.
No, they're not.
Arya...
Bran's home, too.
( crows cawing )
You came home.
I saw you at the crossroads.
You saw me?
I see quite a lot now.
Bran has... visions.
I thought you might go
to King's Landing.
So did I.
Why would you go back there?
Cersei's on her list of names.
Who else is on your list?
Most of them are dead already.
Where did you get this?
Littlefinger gave it to me.
Littlefinger?
He's here?
He has declared for House Stark.
Why would he give you a dagger?
- He thought I'd want it.
- SANSA: Why?
Because it was meant to kill me.
The cutthroat...
after your fall?
Why would a cutthroat
have a Valyrian steel dagger?
Someone very wealthy
wanted me dead.
He's not a generous man.
He wouldn't give you anything
unless he thought he was
getting something back.
- It doesn't matter.
- What do you mean it doesn't matter?
I don't want it.
Are you sure?
ARYA: It's Valyrian steel.
It's wasted on a cripple.
( people chattering )
( bleating )
Catelyn Stark would be proud.
You kept your vow.
I did next to nothing.
You're too hard
on yourself, my lady.
I'm not a...
Thank you, Podrick.
( raven cawing )
( waves crashing )
Your Grace, there's still
no word from the Unsullied.
Soon.
He will come back to you.
He'd better.
What happened?
Many things.
Many things?
- ( sighs )
- JON: Your Grace.
_
( seagulls screeching )
I wanted you to see it
before we start
hacking it to bits.
Well, this is it.
All we'll ever need.
There is something else I
want to show you, Your Grace.
The children of the
forest made these.
When?
A very long time ago.
They were right here,
standing where we're standing.
Before there were Targaryens
or Starks or Lannisters.
Maybe even before
there were men.
No.
They were here together,
the children and the First Men.
Doing what?
Fighting each other?
They fought together
against their common enemy.
Despite their differences,
despite their suspicions.
Together.
We need to do the same
if we're going to survive.
Because the enemy is real.
It's always been real.
And you say
you can't defeat them
without my armies
and my dragons?
No, I don't think I can.
I will fight for you.
I will fight for the North.
When you bend the knee.
My people...
won't accept a southern ruler.
Not after everything
they've suffered.
They will if their king does.
They chose you to lead them.
They chose you to protect them.
Isn't their survival more
important than your pride?
What is it?
We took Casterly Rock.
That's very good to hear.
Isn't it?
You'll want to discuss
this amongst yourselves.
- Perhaps--
- You will stay.
All my allies are gone.
They've been taken from me while I've
been sitting here on this island.
- You still have the largest armies.
- Who won't be able to eat
because Cersei has taken
all the food from the Reach.
TYRION: Call Grey Worm
and the Unsullied back.
We still have enough ships to carry
the Dothraki to the mainland.
Commit to the blockade
of King's Landing.
- We have a plan. It's still the right plan.
- The right plan!
Your strategy has lost us Dorne,
the Iron Islands, and the Reach.
- If I have underestimated our enemies--
- Our enemies?
Your family, you mean.
Perhaps you don't want
to hurt them after all.
( dragons screeching )
Enough with the clever plans.
I have three large dragons.
I'm going to fly them
to the Red Keep.
We've discussed this.
My enemies are in the Red Keep.
What kind of a queen am I if I'm not
willing to risk my life to fight them?
A smart one.
What do you think I should do?
- I would never presume to--
- I'm at war.
I'm losing.
What do you think I should do?
JON: I never thought that
dragons would exist again.
No one did.
The people who follow you
know that you made
something impossible happen.
Maybe that helps them believe
that you can make other
impossible things happen.
Build a world that's different
from the shit one
they've always known.
But if you use them to melt
castles and burn cities,
you're not different.
You're just more of the same.
( dragons screeching )
( both grunting )
- ( huffs )
- Don't lunge.
( grunting )
Don't go where
your enemy leads you.
BRIENNE: Up.
- And don't--
- Don't fight someone like her in the first place.
Nice sword.
Very nice dagger.
If they haven't contributed the right
amount of grain to the stores,
then I'm afraid they'll have to
make due with what they've brought.
We can't...
It's been a while
since I trained.
I can go and find the master
of arms for you, my lady.
He didn't beat the Hound.
You did.
I want to train with you.
You swore to serve
both my mother's daughters,
didn't you?
BRIENNE:
Move aside, Podrick.
You can't use that, my lady.
It's too small.
I won't cut you.
Don't worry.
I'll try not to.
( grunting )
( grunts, shouts )
- ( shouting )
- ( grunts )
( grunts )
( exhales )
Who taught you how to do that?
No one.
( waves crashing )
( seagulls screeching )
- DAVOS: What do you think of her?
- Who?
( sighs ) I believe you
know of whom I speak.
I think she has a good heart.
A good heart?
I've noticed you staring
at her good heart.
There's no time for that.
I saw the Night King, Davos.
I looked into his eyes.
How many men do we have
in the North to fight him?
10,000? Less?
- Fewer.
- What?
Speaking of good hearts--
Missandei of Naath.
Ser Davos, Lord Snow.
King Snow, isn't it?
No, that doesn't sound right.
- King Jon?
- It doesn't matter.
Forgive me, but may
I ask a question?
Of course.
Your name is Jon Snow, but your
father's name was Ned Stark?
I'm a bastard.
My mother and father
weren't married.
Is the custom
different in Naath?
We don't have marriage in Naath,
so the concept of a
bastard doesn't exist.
That sounds...
liberating.
Why did you leave your homeland?
I was stolen away by slavers.
I'm sorry.
If I may, how did a slave girl
come to advise
Daenerys Targaryen?
She bought me from my
master and set me free.
DAVOS:
That was good of her.
Of course, you're serving
her now, aren't you?
I serve my queen because I
want to serve my queen.
Because I believe in her.
And if you wanted to sail
home to Naath tomorrow?
Then she would give me a ship
and wish me good fortune.
You believe that?
I know it.
All of us who came
with her from Essos,
we believe in her.
She's not our queen
because she's the daughter
of some king we never knew.
She's the queen we chose.
Will you forgive me
if I switch sides?
( bell ringing )
JON: Is that a Greyjoy ship?
( men shouting )
( man shouts )
MAN: Halt!
Jon.
I didn't know you were here.
S-Sansa...
is she all right?
What you did for her...
is the only reason
I'm not killing you.
We heard your uncle
attacked your fleet.
We thought you were dead.
I should be.
DAVOS: Your sister?
Euron has her.
I came to ask the queen
to help me get her back.
The queen is gone.
Where did she go?
- MAN: Get the horses watered!
- ( neighs )
( chatter )
All the gold's safely through
the gates of King's Landing.
Good.
We need to get
the last of these wagons
over the Blackwater Rush
before nightfall.
The head of the line
is ambushed,
the tail will never be able
to reinforce in time.
Well, we are stretched
a bit thin.
With your permission,
flogging stragglers has a
marked effect on mobility.
Let's give them
fair warning first.
These men fought well
at Highgarden.
- ( men grunting )
- MAN: Now, get it on this thing.
- MAN #2: Lift!
- ( men laughing )
- Ser Jaime.
- Rickon.
Dickon.
I hear you fought bravely
at Highgarden.
Your first battle?
And?
It was glorious.
Come on, your father's not here.
All my life, we've been
pledged to House Tyrell.
I knew some of those men.
I hunted with them.
They didn't deserve to die.
But Lady Olenna
chose to betray her queen
and support the Targaryen girl.
So here we are.
I didn't expect it
to smell like that.
Men shit themselves
when they die.
Didn't they teach you that
at fancy lad school?
Well, I learned it
when I was five.
( distant horse neighs )
What?
Listen.
( distant hoofbeats
approaching )
( rumbling )
JAIME: Spears and shields!
Spears and shields!
- What is it?
- BRONN: Get in line!
Spears and shields!
Get in line now!
Form up!
Come on, lads!
Guard those wagons!
Form a line!
MAN: Round those spears!
( men shrieking in distance )
MAN: Shield wall!
Fill the gaps!
- Randyll: Archers, steady!
- MAN #2: Hold together!
- Archers!
- Look alive!
Get tight!
MAN: Get in line, boys!
- Ready!
- Here they come!
- ( distant men shrieking )
- ( hoofbeats approaching )
- ( hoofbeats pounding )
- ( men shrieking, whooping )
( all shrieking )
MAN: Courage, lads! Courage!
MAN #2: Wait! Wait for it!
Spears out!
( men grunt )
- JAIME: Spears out!
- RANDYLL: Steady! Hold the line!
- Get back to King's Landing.
- I'm not abandoning my army.
BRONN: You're the commander,
not a damn infantryman.
Those fuckers are
about to swamp us.
We can hold them off.
( dragon roaring )
( roaring )
Dracarys!
( pants )
( men screaming )
( screaming continues )
( screams echoing )
( Dothraki shrieking )
JAIME: Hold the line!
Hold!
- BRONN: Hold it, lads!
- Hold the line!
- MAN: Throw it!
- ( grunts, screams )
- ( grunts )
- MAN: Hold!
( men grunting )
( men shouting )
MAN: Draw!
Loose!
( dragon roars )
( men screaming )
- Archers!
- MAN: Archers!
Archers, with me!
- MAN: Archers, to the line!
- MAN #2: To the line!
- Nock!
- MAN: Nock!
- ( dragon roaring )
- Draw!
- Loose!
- MAN: Loose!
MAN: Run!
( men screaming )
Qyburn's scorpion is over there.
Go get it, then.
I can't shoot with one hand.
- ( horse neighs )
- BRONN: Come on!
( shouts )
( grunting )
( horse screaming )
( shouts )
( man screaming )
( horse bellowing )
- ( men screaming )
- MAN: Need help!
( screaming )
( men screaming )
( dragon roaring )
( Dothraki shrieking )
( grunts )
Where are you?
( roaring )
( men screaming )
( Dothraki shrieking
in distance )
( screams echoing )
_
( horse screaming )
( screams echoing )
( dragon roaring )
Take cover!
Come on, you fucker.
Dracarys.
( roaring )
( yelps )
( dragon crying out )
( panting )
( men screaming )
( roaring )
( grunting )
Flee, you idiot.
- Come on, boy. Come on!
- ( horse neighs )
You idiot.
You fucking idiot.
( grunts )
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com